brock**ellefson**

about

406-670-1796 1104 South Montana Ave. Bozeman, MT 59718 Currently studying Computer Science at Montana State University. I am contantly pursing anything that can help me improve my coding, for instance, I am currently developing my first app. Reading multiple textbooks over the subject, learning more on how to complete it day by day

areas of expertise

Customer Service

Programming in: Java, C, ARMV8, Blitz Basic, Python, Perl

OSHA Certified to operate forklifts

Computer Repair

Remote and local tech support

education

Since 2014 Bachelors in Computer Science

work experience

2015-Now Cardinal Distribution

Lead Wine Loader .

2014 - 2015 Staples EasyTec

Computer salesman and technician.

2013 - 2014 Red Lobster

Dishwasher, Baker

2013 - 2013 Dairy Queen

Grill Cook, Cashier

misc.

2017 **Association of Computing Machinery**

http://www.cs.montana.edu/ acm/

A student organization here at MSU dedicated to helping students who are going into the Computer Science Field. Meet regularly to plan new events, recruit new people, and reach out to local businesses for tours and advice.